System Dynamic Society; Records ua435
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Conferences, 1976-2018
  - Nijmegen, Netherlands, 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
    - Papers, 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Schaffernicht, Martin, "LaTina – An online system for teaching and learning stock-and-flow thinking skills", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Scheffran, Jurgen with Todd BenDor and Bruce Hannon, "An Exploration of Competition and Cooperation Through a Multi-Agent Dynamic-Game Model of Fishery Management", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Schild, Heinz, "Traffic Shifts in a Comprehensive Truck Toll System, A Real-World Multi-Agent Based Simulation Case Study", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Schmid, Lukas with Marcel Loher and Roland Waibel, "Strategic Decisions in the Transition to Deregulated Markets", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Scholz-Reiter, Bernd with Salima Delhoum, "The Supply Net Game", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Sedehi, Habib, "GAIM (Gestione Accoglienza IMmigrati): A System Dynamics Model for Immigration "housing" Management", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Serrano, Maria Cristina with Gerly Carolina Ariza Zabala, Ricardo Sotaquirá, Jorge Andrick Parra Valencia and Lilia Nayibe, "From Individualistic to Collective Rationality in Simulation Games for Social Sustainability", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Shakouri, Hamed with Zahra Esmaeeli and Asgar Sedighi, "Investigation of pricing impact on the energy consumption behavior of the household sector by a system dynamics model", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Shumarova, Elitsa with Paul Swatman, "The Dynamics of Innovation in Electronic Networks - a System Dynamics Perspective on Sustainable IT Innovation", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Sim, Mong Soon with Kah Wah Lai, Seow Buay Seah, Wai Gea Khoo, Chow Ying Lee and Kah Chee Yee, "Simulating impacts of disruption in a network of chemical manufacturing plants and supporting infrastructures", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Skraba, Andrej with Miroljub Kljajic, Davorin Kofjac, Matevz Bren and Mico Mrkaic, "Cobweb Model in System Dynamics Form - Hyperincursive Perspective", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Soo, Joyce with Mats Svensson, "Sustainable Management of Shrimp Farming: A Case Study in Ninh Thuan, Vietnam", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Soto-Torres, M. Dolores with Ramon Fernandez-Lechon, "Feedback Processes in Economic Growth: Relations between Hours Worked and Labour Productivity", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Stave, Krystyna with Michael Dwyer, "Lessons from LUTAQ: Building systems thinking capacity into land use, transportation, and air quality planning in Las Vegas, NV", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Struben, Jeroen, "Alternative fuel vehicles turning the corner? A product lifecycle model with heterogeneous technologies", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Struben, Jeroen, "Identifying challenges for sustained adoption of alternative fuel vehicles and infrastructure", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Sveen, Finn with Ying Qian, Stefanie Hillen, Jaziar Radianti and Jose Gonzalez, "A Dynamic Approach to Vulnerability and Risk Analysis of the Transition to eOperations", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Syahril, Shanty with Muhammad Tasrif, A. Taufik Mukhith and Lucentezza Napitupulu, "Group Model Building Intervention in Developing Country: Lesson Learned from Developing Strategies for Clean Air", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Tabacaru, Mihaela, "What We Don't Measure about Human Resources: Towards a Conceptual Framework for Analysing the Role of Soft Variables", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Takahashi, Yutaka with Nobuhide Tanaka and Akira Uchino, "Nomadic Beer Game on Computer Networks", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Takahashi, Yutaka, "Stock Flow Diagram Making with Incomplete Information about Time Properties of Variables", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Tan, Burcu, "A Dynamic Analysis of Long Term Impacts of Genetically Modified Crops", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Thompson, James, "Making Sense Of U.S. Health Care System Dynamics", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Tilebein, Meike, "Principles of Emergence. A Generic Framework of Firms as Agent-Based Complex Adaptive Systems", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Toussaint, Pieter with Margaret Williamson, Geoff McDonnell and Øystein Nytro, "Modeling the Communications Dimension of Clinical Work and Medication Errors", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Trijssenaar, Anton, "Jeu-de-Joule: a conceptual earthly energy model", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Ulli-Beer, Silvia with Suzanne Bruppacher, Stefan Groesser, Stefanie Geisshusler, Matthias Mueller, Mohammad Mojtahedzadeh, Markus Schwaninger, Fran Ackermann, David Andersen, George Richardson, Roland Stulz and Ruth Kaufmann-Hayoz, "Understanding and accelerating the diffusion process of energy-efficient buildings", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Vaishnav, Chintan with Ali Khakifirooz and Martine Devos, "Punishing by Rewards: When the Performance Bell-curve Stops Working For You", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Van Den Durpel, Luc with Dave Wade and Abdellatif Yacout, "DANESS: a system dynamics code for the holistic assessment of nuclear energy system strategies", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - van Oppen, Willem, "Offensive KPI's: Coordinating strategy and operations in interorganizational service supply networks", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Vargas Guerrero, Germán with Isaac Dyner, "Evolutionary Effectiveness's Dynamics of Enterprise Innovation", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Vennix, Jac with Etiënne Rouwette, Andreas Groessler, Jack Homer and Roberta Spencer, "Welcome by Conference Organizing Committee", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Viladent, Christian, "A deterministic model to assess the impact of HAART in Sub-Saharan countries.An application to Botswana", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Visser, Max, "The System Dynamics of Group Facilitation and Communication", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Vogstad, Klaus with Steen Koekebakker, Fridthjof Ollmar, Fredrik Olsen and Tor Handaa, "Stochasticity in electricity markets: Combining system dynamics with financial economics", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Vojtko, Viktor with Stanislava Mildeova, Jan Trojacek and Ingeborg Nemcova, "Market Dynamics for Decision Support in Marketing", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Voyer, John with Gregory Stevens, Charles McCormick and Liam Shaw, "Non-Standard Basic Monthly Earnings Calculations For Long-Term Disability Insurance Contracts: A System Dynamics Examination", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Weber, Lars with Veit Schulz, "Voter's Power in Aging Societies", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Xu, Bo with Haiyan Yan, "System Archetype Analysis on Some Problems of Chinese Enterprises Cross-border M&A", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Yamaguchi, Kaoru, "Integration of Real and Monetary Sectors - System Dynamics Macroeconomic Modeling", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Yan, Haiyan with Bo Xu, "Systems Thinking on the Demand and Training for International Business Talents", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Young, Showing with Shyh-Jane Li, Chun-Fu Chen and Yu-Ying Huang, "To investigate players' behavior when price variable is put in the Beer Game", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Yuliani, Dewi with Muhammad Tasrif, "Understanding Community Empowerment Process: A Case Study of a Rural Locality in Indonesia", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
      - Zagonel, Aldo with Thomas Corbet, "Levels of Confidence in System Dynamics Modeling: A Pragmatic Approach to Assessment of Dynamic Models", 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
    - Conference Photos, 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
    - Sponsor Notes, 2006 July 23-2006 July 27
  - Boston, MA, USA, 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
    - Conference Website, 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
    - Call for Papers, 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
    - Abstract Proceedings, 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
    - Papers, 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - AbdelGawad, Ahmed with Bahaa Aly Abdel-Aleem, Mohamed Saleh and Pål Davidsen, "Automated Eigenvalue Analysis of System Dynamics Models", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Abou Ali, Tarek with Khaled Wahba, "Assessment of Egyptian Software Export Capabilities Using a System Dynamics Approach", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Adamides, Emmanuel with Yeoryios Stamboulis and Nikolaos Pomonis, "Modularity and Strategic Flexibility: A Cogntive and Dynamic Perspective", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Ahmed, Fadl with Khaled Wahba and Abdallah Ahmed, "The Dynamics of Glucose Regulatory System: An Educational Tool for the Students of First Medical Year", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Akcam, Bahadir with Victor Asal, "The Dynamics of Ethnic Terrorism", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Al-Qirem, Raed with Alfredo Moscardini and Mohamed Loutfi, "The Use Of System Dynamics Models To Evaluate The Credit-Worthiness Of Firms", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Alkemper, Jens with Don Mango, "Simulation of the Reinsurance Market using Agent-Based Modeling", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - An, Lianjun with Bala Ramachandran, "System Dynamics Model to Understand Demand-Conditioning Dynamics in Supply Chains", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Anderson, Edward with Kyle Lewis, "An Initial Dynamic Model of Transactive Memory Systems", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Arango, Santiago, "Oscillatory Behavior as a Function of Market Complexity: Experiments on Commodity Cycles", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Arenas, Fernando, "An Adaptive Expectations Approach to the Mechanisms of Transmission Model of the Central Bank of Colombia", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Arthur, Daniel, "Upscaling Diffusion Models to Represent General Purpose Technologies for Industry Modelling", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Askar, Mohamed with Karim Assabghy and Syed Imam, "Business Dynamics Exploratory Model for Reviewing Industry in Developing Countries: The Case of Egyptian Automotive Industry", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Baik, Hojong with Antonio Trani and Michel Turcotte, "A Transportation Systems Analysis Model to Study the Impact of the Small Aircraft Transportation Systems (SATS)", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bakken, Bent Erik, "Special Session: Military Roundtable", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bakken, Bent Erik with Pål Ostbye and Arne Roksund, "Transforming a Military Personnel Policy – Learning from a Model Supported Intervention", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Ballardin, Giorgio, "Environmental Benefits and Economic Rationale of Expanding the Italian Natural Gas Private Car Fleet", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Barlas, Yaman with Suat Bog, "Automated Dynamic Pattern Testing, Parameter Calibration and Policy Improvement", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bartoszczuk, Pawel, "Optimisation of Consumption with Emission", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bassi, Andrea with Tobias Lorenz, "Management Flight Simulators: Development of a Multiplayer, Asymmetric, Network, ILE", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bayer, Steffen with David Gann and Ammon Salter, "Balancing Work – Bidding Strategies and Workload Dynamics in a Project-Based Professional Service Organisation", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - BenDor, Todd with Sara Metcalf, Lauren Fontenot and Brandi Sangunett, "A Decision Support System for Emerald Ash Borer Eradication Using Spatial-Dynamic Modeling", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - BenDor, Todd with Sara Metcalf, "Conceptual Modeling and Dynamic Simulation of Brownfield Redevelopment", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Berard, Céline with Martin Cloutier and Luc Cassivi, "Performance Evaluation of Management Information Systems in Clinical Trials: A System Dynamics Approach", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bianchi, Carmine with Graham Winch, "'Stunted Growth' in Small Firms: How to Turn Them Round and Unleash Their Potential", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bianchi, Carmine with Enzo Bivona, "Using System Dynamics ILEs in Service Business Interventions", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bivona, Enzo with Giovan Battista Montemaggiore, "Evaluating Fleet Maintenance and Management Strategies through a System Dynamics Model in a City Bus Company", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bivona, Enzo with Francesco Ceresia, "Designing Long Term Oriented Policies to Build Strong Manufacturer-Dealer Relationships: A System Dynamics Approach", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Black, Jason, "Diffusion Of Demand Response Technology In Electricity Systems", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Borshchev, Andrei with Nathaniel Osgood, Geoff McDonnell, Mark Paich, Hazhir Rahmandad, Mark Heffernan, Sara Metcalf and Christopher Johnson, "Workshop: Agent-Based Modeling: Why Bother?", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bourne, Mary Lou with Michael Deaton, "The Dynamics of Identity Theft: A Comparison of Symptomatic and Systemic Solutions", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Boyer, Jeffrey with John Elter, "The Dynamic Behavior of a Zero-to-Landfill Strategy for Consumer Products", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Braun, Bill, "The Dynamics of Economic Value Depletion: A Proposal for Accelerated Feedback Loops in Production and Purchasing Decisions", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Brehmer, Berndt with Fredrik Elg, "Heuristics in Dynamic Decision Making: Coping with the Time Constants of a Dynamic Task by Doing Something Else", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Buendia, Fernando, "Increasing Returns to Economic Activity Agglomeration", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bueno, Newton, "Stabilization Policy Debate, Control Theory and System Dynamics Metholology", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Bulbul, Ali Afsin, "Capturing Project Dynamics with a New Project Management Tool: Project Management Simulation Model (PMSM)", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Burke, James with John Hummel, "System Dynamics Characterizations of the Defense Industrial Base Critical Infrastructure", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Burns, James with Balaji Janamanchi, "Project Dynamics with Applications to Change Management and Earned Value Tracking", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Burns, James with Balaji Janamanchi, "Offshoring Knowledge Worker Jobs – Boom or Burst for the US Economy", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Burton, Lester with Seetha Coleman-Kammula, John Sterman, David Andersen and George Richardson, "A System Dynamics Study of a Commodity Plastics Industry", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Campbell, Deborah, "Special Session: Diversity Roundtable", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Capelo, Carlos with João Dias, "Double Learning and Performance Improvement with the Balanced Scorecard – A Simulation-Based Experiment", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Cavalieri-D'Oro, Edoardo with Michael Golay, "Preparing for the Near-Term Deployment of New Nuclear Fission Technologies: A SD Analysis of the Nuclear Market's Behaviours", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Cavana, Robert, "Revisiting Medium Term Macro-economic Scenarios (1985 – 1995) Generated by a System Dynamics Model of the New Zealand Economy", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Chang, Liang-Cheng with Yi-Ming Tu, "Attempt to Integrate System Dynamics and UML in Business Process Modeling", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Chen, Jie, "Modeling Shanghai Real Estate Market", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Chen, Yibai with Hongbing Zhu, Min Jiang and Yonggen Yuan, "Pleasantly Surprised in Applying Systems Thinking to Teaching High School Students", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Chen, Yu with Yuqin Yao, "Research on the Change Process of the Curved Roof of Chinese Ancient Architecture by System Dynamics", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Chung, Ik Jae, "A Dynamic Approach to Social Amplification through Internet", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Cloutier, Martin with Céline Berard and Luc Cassivi, "Diffusion of an Innovative Biotechnology: The Case of Plant-Derived Vaccines using System Dynamics", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Cooke, David with Thomas Rohleder, "A Conceptual Model of Operational Risk", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Cooper, Kenneth with Thomas Kelly and Sharon Els, "Special Session: Program Management Workshop", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Crespo, Adolfo, "Front-end, Back-end and Integration Issues in Virtual Supply Chain Dynamics Modeling", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Cronin, Matthew with Cleotilde Gonzalez, "Understanding the Building Blocks of Dynamic Systems: What Is the Problem, Really?", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Cumenal, Didier, "Simulating Organizational Change: Moving and Shaking", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Daneshgari, Parviz with Frank Murdock, "Operational Model for Improving System Productivity of Distributors: Internal Cost Drivers", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Dangerfield, Brian, "Towards a Transition to a Knowledge Economy: How System Dynamics is Helping Sarawak Plan its Economic and Social Evolution", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Dauelsberg, Lori with Alexander Outkin, "Modeling Economic Impacts to Critical Infrastructures in a System Dynamics Framework", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Deegan, Michael, "Extreme Event Policy Design: A Conceptual Model to Analyze Policies and the Policy Process for Natural Hazards", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Derrick, Sonja with Graham Winch, Beryl Badger, Joan Chandler, Jenny Lovett and Tim Nokes, "Evaluating the Impacts of Time-Reduction Legislation on Junior Doctor Training and Service", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Dhawan, Rajat, "Usefulness of Probabilistic System Dynamics in Dynamic Decision Making", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Diker, Vedat with Robert Allen, "It's About Time: The Why and How of Using XML for Developing an Interchange Standard for System Dynamics Models", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Dogan, Gökhan with John Sterman, "When Less Leads to More: Phantom Ordering in the Beer Game?", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Dudley, Richard, "A Generic Look at Payments for Environmental Services: Plan or Scam?", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Duggan, Jim, "Using Multiple Objective Optimisation to Generate Policy Insights for System Dynamics Models", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Duggan, Jim, "Workshop: Exploring Optimal Trade-Offs in a Two-Actor Beer Game Model", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Dvornik, Josko with Ante Munitic and Frane Mitrovic, "SD Simulation Modelling of Organisational Business System of Management of Material & Informational Flows in Productive Company", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Dyner, Isaac, "Energy Contribution to Sustainable Rural Livelihoods in Developing Countries: A System Dynamics Approach", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Edgar, William with C. Lance Durham and Aparna Higgins, "The AIDS Epidemic: Integrating System Dynamics and Gaming for Strategic Simulation", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Elf, Marie with Maria Poutilova, "The Care Planning Process – A Case for System Dynamics", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Ellis, R. Evan, "Paramilitary Demobilization in Colombia – Insights from a System-Dynamics Based Seminar Game", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Els, Sharon, "Special Session: Business Roundtable", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Emmi, Philip with Craig Forster and James Mills, "Insights into the Dynamics of a Carbon-Based Metropolis", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Ewers, Mary, "Combining Hydrology and Economics in a Systems Dynamics Approach: Modeling Water Resources for the San Juan Basin", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Exelby, David with John Holt and Sion Cave, "Systems Modeling of Lancashire Drug Intervention Programme (DIP)", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Fisher, Diana, "Workshop: Modeling Dynamic Systems: Lessons for a First Course", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Fletcher, Michael, "The Dynamics of Analytic Collaboration", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Flury, Christian with Gabriele Mack and Birgit Kopainsky, "A Composite Optimisation-Simulation Model for the Analysis of the Dynamic Interactions in the Swiss Milk and Meat Market", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Flynn, Hilary with Andrew Ford, "A System Dynamics Study of Carbon Cycling and Electricity Generation from Energy Crops", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Fogel, Jonah, "Learning to See a Brighter Future for Morgan County, TN", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Ford, David with Tim Taylor and Scott Johnson, "Why Good Projects Go Bad: Managing Development Projects Near Tipping Points", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Franck, Travis, "Quantifying the Cost Uncertainty of Climate Stabilization Policies", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Franco, Douglas, "Insurance Dynamics: Managing Information Flows", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Fryling, Meg, "ERP Implementation Dynamics", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Garcia, Rosanna with Anand Nair, "Allocation of Resources in Exploration and Exploitation of Technologies: Re-evaluation Using an Adaptive Agent Application", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Gary, Shayne with Robert Wood, "Mental Models, Decision Making, and Performance in Complex Tasks", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Ge, Zhou with Yonggen Yuan, "Systematic Dynamics Thinking in Innovative Teaching", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Georgantzas, Nicholas with Nadezhda Peeva and Howard Weinberg, "Disruptive Innovation Diffusion", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Getmansky, Mila, "Limits of Arbitrage: Understanding How Hedge Funds Fail", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Glass-Husain, Will, "Workshop: Making your Simulation Run on the World Wide Web", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Goncalves, Paulo with John Sterman, "Overordering Games in Supply Chains", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Gonzalez, Jose, "Special Convened Session: Critical Infrastructure", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Goodman, Michael, "Special Moments - Special Places", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Graham, Alan with Jeremy Godfrey, "Achieving Win-Win in a Regulatory Dispute: Managing 3G Competition", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Groesser, Stefan, "Modeling the Health Insurance System of Germany: A System Dynamics Approach", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Groesser, Stefan, "Does Experience or an Education in System Dynamics Help People to Solve Simple, Dynamic Problems? – A Laboratory Experiment", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Groessler, Andreas, "An Exploratory System Dynamics Model of Strategic Manufacturing Capabilities", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Guneralp, Burak, "Towards Coherent Loop Dominance Analysis: Progress in Eigenvalue Elasticity Analysis", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Haraldsson, Hördur with Harald Sverdrup and Salim Belyazid, "The Tyranny of Small Steps I: Discovery of an Archetypical Behaviour", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Haraldsson, Hördur with Harald Sverdrup, "On Aspects of System Analysis and Dynamics Workflow", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Haraldsson, Hördur with Rannveig Olafsdottir, "A Modelling Approach for Evaluating the Pre-Industrial Natural Carrying Capacity of the Human Population in Iceland", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Haraldsson, Hördur with Harald Sverdrup, "Making Art into a Science: Adaptive Learning Behaviour and Managing Group Modelling Innovation Processes", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Heinbokel, John with P. Jeffrey Potash, "Endogenous Human Behaviors in a Pneumonic Plague Simulation: Psychological and Behavioral Theories as Small "Generic" Models", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Hines, James, "Workshop: How to Visit a Great Model Like Yours", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Hirsch, Gary with Guy Stuart, Jay Rosengard and Don Johnston, "SymBanc™: A Simulator for Microfinance Institutions", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21
      - Hirsch, Gary, "Health Policy Special Interest Group Session Notes", 2005 July 17-2005 July 21